<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World, ProfileMeActivity!</string>
	<string name="app_name">ProfileMe</string>
	<string name="app_title_email">I have just completed a profile using the mobile
		app
		Profile Me. It tells me about 7 major personality traits and how to
		read them. I’m looking forward to trying the next app, Profile Match,
		which will show me how to communicate more effectively with anyone I
		profile.</string>



	<string name="app_text">“The Face - How to get your ideal careers to match
		your personality” is dedicated to Reading Human Traits; and in
		particular it is written for secondary school students, their parents
		and teachers. The Biggest life decision a student will make is what
		career they should follow when they leave school. The book introduces
		the techniques and the advantages to being able to read your traits,
		understand your personality and how that relate to career selection.
		This book covers 20 traits that are readily recognisable and that have
		a direct correlation to particular careers. In other words; it’s a
		book on how to selecting a career for optimum success and
		enjoyment.\n\n

		It will help you recognise your strengths and how to
		handle stress. It
		also give you insight into how others see you.\n\n

		It
		is the first in a series of seven books on Human Pattern Recognition
		and the four related fields that form The Art of Reading People.
	</string>
	
	<string name="app_hw_it_works">We have set out to give you an introduction to how
		to read your personality traits and those of other people. There are a
		number of traits that you should know; traits that will tell you how
		other see you. Having this knowledge will give you more control over
		your life and help you to create far better relationships. The App
		will help you to create better and stronger first impressions.\n\n
		Face Reading pre-dates all levels of psychology and was the only
		technique we had to evaluate the behaviors and personalities of other
		people. It is still proving to be the best method available to
		everyone. People can cheat on a written questionnaire about themselves
		but they cannot lie about their facial features. These written test
		(Psychometric profiles) provide common language for practical
		psychology oriented people, but they fail to account adequately for
		human diversity. Face Reading has no such shortfall.  If you can read
		their facial features you can read their personalities. You will
		understand how they prefer to think and behave how they prefer to be
		interacted with.  To understand other people, you first need to
		understand yourself and how other people consciously and unconsciously
		see you.  Profile me is the App for doing just that.
	</string>


	<string name="app_trait2_desc">Are you a person who is quick to make friends or
		more discerning about who you make friends with? How you react when
		meeting new people and how they see you and respond to you is
		determined by the height of the eyebrows. People with high set
		eyebrows have a natural tendency to require more personal space when
		first meeting new people. They generally wait to be introduced while
		those with low set eyebrows are more likely to introduce themselves
		when you first meet. How high set or low set are your eyebrows?\n\n

		The trait is measured by comparing the vertical space between the
		underside of the eyebrow and the top of the eye compared to the actual
		height of the eye when the person is looking straight ahead and
		relaxed. Taking a line vertically through the pupil of the eye and
		compare the height of the eye to that of the gap between the eye and
		the eyebrow.\n\n

		Would the eye fit into the space above the eye
		aperture and under the
		eyebrow? If it just fits it would be a medium
		score. If the space is
		smaller than the height of the eye the person is
		viewed to be affable,
		Type A, while in the case where there is more
		space the person is
		viewed to be more discriminating, Type C\n\n

		Type A
		has low set eyebrows. By nature you focus on specifics, singling
		out
		your target, you move in close. You come across as being very easy
		to
		meet and very friendly. Someone who is very easy to get along with.
		When you meet people who have high set eyebrows, adopt a more formal
		approach. Don’t move into their space too quickly or you\’ll scare
		them
		off. Be careful about making physical contact, even if it’s a
		light
		touch on the arm, or they might take it the wrong way.\n\n

		Type
		B’s fit mid way between the two extremes. You\’ll find some people
		over friendly while others seem more reserved. Generally though,
		you\’ll get on well with both groups. Be prepared to have those with
		low set eyebrows stand closer to you, while giving more personal space
		to those with high set eyebrows.\n\n

		Type C’s have high set eyebrows.
		By nature you are more discriminating
		than those with low set eyebrows.
		You appear to others with low set
		eyebrows as being more formal and
		less approachable. In order to
		appear more friendly wear softer colors,
		be more expressive and speak
		with warmth in your voice. Learn to smile
		more when meeting people for
		the first time. You are just as friendly
		as anyone else once you get
		to know the other person, so show it.

	</string>

	<string name="app_trait3_desc">Tolerance is about how we each respond to our
		surroundings; the way we view our environment. Tolerance is indicated
		by the Width of the Eyes. The wider the eyes are set apart the wider
		the view and the more tolerant the person is in the moment.\n\n

		Is the
		gap between the eyes wider than the width of each eye, the same
		width,
		or is the gap between the eyes narrower than the width of each
		eye?\n\n

		Which one is the width of your eyes most like?\n\n

		Type A’s
		have closer set eyes. By nature you are intolerant of errors. You
		have
		a keen sense of priority and take immediate action to correct
		things
		that aren’t quite right. Punctuality is important to you. You
		are
		precise and attention to detail is important. When you focus on a
		task
		or you are under stress, others will see you as just tolerant or
		feel
		you lack tolerance. You are quickly irritated by interruptions,
		sloppy
		work and things that are not completed on time. Because you are
		so
		focused on what you are doing, you can easily get lost in your
		thoughts and activities. Make sure you come up for air now and again,
		and check in to see what’s happening around you. Your strength is that
		you pay attention to detail and stay focused on the task at hand. This
		is also a trait that can cause relationship conflicts.\n\n

		Type B’s
		have evenly spaced eyes. You are the mediator. The person who is
		balanced between the type A and type C. You are more tolerant than
		Type A and more focused than Type C. To Type A you appear to be more
		like Type C and to Type C you appear to be more like Type A\n\n

		Type C
		have wider set eyes. By nature you are tolerant of errors. You come
		across as being very laid back and very easy to get along with. You
		have a tendency to put things off until tomorrow and you can be easily
		distracted and take on too many things at once. The challenge for you
		is to stay focused on what you are doing. Try not to take on more than
		you can handle. You may tolerate too much, and when this happens you
		need to create more boundaries or otherwise people can take advantage
		of your good nature. If you have a tendency to be late, start out
		earlier than usual in order to get to appointments and meetings on
		time, as others can take your lateness as tardiness or disinterest.
		This is also a trait that can cause relationship conflicts, especially
		when the other person has low tolerance.\n\n
	
		</string>
	<string name="app_trait4_desc"> The Philtrum is the grooved area between the base
		of the nose and the upper lip. The length of the philtrum indicates
		the form of a person’s sense of humor. It indicates how a person
		reacts to the comments of others; whether they take those words and
		comments personally or they appear more detached and unaffected.\n\n

		What is the length of the Philtrum in comparison to the over-all
		facial
		proportion?\n\n

		Type A’s can take other peoples comments and
		criticism personally. If
		someone makes a critical remark, ask what was
		meant by it and explore
		the comment further to avoid misunderstanding.
		Remember some people
		with the longer gap can come across as sarcastic
		although their
		intention was just to be amusing; which can get taken
		the wrong way.\n\n

		Type B’s fit mid way between the two extremes.
		You’ll find some people
		have a dry sense of humor, possibly slightly
		sarcastic, while others
		seem to take your words more personally.
		Generally though, you’ll get
		on well with both groups, very often being
		the mediator between type
		A’s and type C’s. Be prepared to watch what
		you say to those with the
		smaller philtrum and don’t take the words of
		those with the longer
		philtrum personally.\n\n

		Type C’s have a dry sense
		of humor, which those in tune with you will
		enjoy. However not
		everyone, especially those with a small philtrum,
		will understand the
		subtlety of your humor. To some you can also come
		across as being very
		sarcastic and cutting, which may not be your
		intent. Those with the
		short philtrum can take a harmless comment and
		feel very hurt, so be
		careful that it does not have a cutting edge.
		remember others may miss
		the subtlety of your humor.
	
	</string>

	<string name="app_trait5_desc">This trait is one of expression and it is seen in
		the shape and size of the lips. The lips are an indicator of the way
		we respond to situations and people before we consciously thinking
		about how to respond; how we demonstrate what we are feeling inside.
		It is an impulsive reaction to events, situations and other people. It
		is both a representation of our style of giving and our verbal
		style.\n\n

		You measure the size of the lips compared to the over-all
		facial
		proportions. Do the lips look smaller, larger or balanced
		compared to
		the persons face?\n\n

		Type A’s are more reflective by
		nature. Those with a thin Upper Lip are by
		nature concise when
		speaking. They prefer to talk facts with short
		explanations, prefer to
		be concise . Those with the smaller lower lip
		are by nature more
		reflective and think more before giving of their
		time, their
		possessions and of themselves. They appreciate interests
		that are
		expressed non verbally and when giving do so with a lot of
		significance and meaning.\n\n

		Type B are between the two extremes. The
		person who is balanced between
		the type A and type C. They are more
		verbal and quick to give than
		Type A and more reflective before
		responding than Type C. To Type A’s
		they appear to be more like Type
		C’s and to Type C’s they appear to be
		more like Type A’s.\n\n

		Type C’s
		are those with a full upper lip and are by nature more talkative.
		Those with the full lower lip are by nature more generous in the
		moment. They are open and immediate with their words and their deeds;
		often giving without thinking and speaking at length. They will appear
		to be more emotional than the other types. They need to talk and need
		to express themselves and with this they are quick to give; often
		giving too liberally, something that they may regret later.
	
		</string>

	<string name="app_trait6_desc">
		How exposed or concealed the eyelids appear to be
		indicates how a person
		looks at the world. It indicates how they judge
		what they see and how
		they process information. Do they like to analyze
		information to
		arrive at an answer or do they prefer to first look at
		the big picture
		and make their decisions from there. Do they want all
		the facts or
		just want you to get to the point?\n\n

		Measure by looking
		at the eyelid and the epicanthic fold (the fold of skin
		above the
		eyelid), are the eyelids exposed, semi covered or fully
		uncovered by
		the epicanthic fold? If the eyelids are totally exposed
		or they do not
		have an epicanthic fold at all, these are the Type A’s.
		Semi covered
		eyelids are Type B’s and the fully concealed are Type
		C’s.\n\n

		Type A’s
		are less inclined to analyze situations and information. It
		doesn’t
		indicate that you don’t analyze, but more the trait indicates
		you like
		people to get to the bottom line. You are by nature decisive
		and you
		focus outwardly on what needs to be done. You just want the
		big picture
		and you’re action driven. You have an immediate
		understanding of what
		is being said and like to act on it right away.
		This trait also
		indicates that you don’t need all of the information
		up front to make a
		decision. If necessary you will go back later to
		check for any
		additional details. Try not to cut people off in the
		midst of their
		conversation or finish their sentences for them, or
		they will feel that
		you are not interested in what they are saying.\n\n

		Type B’s have
		eyelids which are half covered by, or very close to the
		epicanthic
		fold. These are the balancers; the mediators. They are
		viewed by Type
		A’s as being Type C’s, while Type C’s see them more
		like Type A’s. You
		are likely to gather more information before making
		decisions than the
		type A’s, yet you will be viewed by the type C’s to
		still make your
		decisions too quickly. Learn to speed up when dealing
		with Type A’s and
		don’t cut Type C’s off when they are talking.\n\n

		Type C’s are by
		nature very analytical. They focus inwardly on what they
		feel about a
		situation. They need to understand how and why things
		work, which makes
		them reluctant to make decisions until their
		questions have been
		completely satisfied. Try not to over analyze
		everything, otherwise
		you’ll find the project you are working on is
		being held up by your
		need to assess every step along the way. Decide
		what is most important
		for now, then check the other details later
		rather than hold up
		progress. When talking with individuals who want
		the bottom line, keep
		your responses to the point.
	
		</string>
	<string name="app_trait7_desc">Some people appear to have a depth of color and a
		sparkle in the color in their eyes. They appear to be warm and
		inviting while others are cooler and less inviting. Often those with
		magnetic eyes are seen to be flirting when in fact they are not. The
		level of magnetism has a strong impact on how people see each other
		and how they open up to each other. Being able to recognize and
		understand the effects of magnetism can save us from a lot of
		embarrassment. Magnetism is a trait that can change throughout our
		lives, depending on how we view and respond to the world and our
		circumstances.\n\n

		Do the colored area (the Iris) of the eyes have a
		depth of color and a
		strong sparkle?\n\n

		First be aware that there is no
		Type A in this trait, well there is but it
		is related to another trait
		relating to the 3 different levels of
		stress, which will be covered in
		future Apps.\n\n

		When you look at a person’s eyes, do you feel drawn
		towards them? If you
		do, then they are magnetic Type C’s. If your
		wondering why other
		people seem to attract more people to them and they
		appear to be more
		popular, the magnetic quality of their eyes is one
		major reason.\n\n

		Type B’s have a lack of eye sparkle. Don’t worry
		though as this can change
		when a person decides to be more outgoing and
		focusing more on having
		fun. The less stress they have in their life
		contributes to adding
		sparkle to the eyes.\n\n

		Type C’s have a depth of
		the color in their eyes. They have a magnetic
		quality and a sparkle
		that attracts people to them. People with
		magnetism are more alert and
		often more fun. Other people get a
		feeling of trust when they look into
		their eyes. Strangers will come
		up to them and without any reservations
		they will tell them their
		deepest secrets. 
	
	</string>

	
	<string name="app_trait2_type_a">
		Type A has low set eyebrows. By nature you focus on
		specifics, singling out your target, you move in close. You come
		across as being very easy to meet and very friendly. Someone who is
		very easy to get along with. When you meet people who have high set
		eyebrows, adopt a more formal approach. Don’t move into their space
		too quickly or you will scare them off. Be careful about making
		physical
		contact, even if its a light touch on the arm, or they might
		take it
		the wrong way.
	</string>
	<string name="app_trait2_type_b">
		Type B’s fit mid way between the two extremes.
		You’ll find some people
		over friendly while others seem more reserved.
		Generally though,
		you’ll get on well with both groups. Be prepared to
		have those with
		low set eyebrows stand closer to you, while giving more
		personal space
		to those with high set eyebrows.


	</string>
	<string name="app_trait2_type_c">
		Type C’s have high set eyebrows. By nature you are
		more discriminating
		than those with low set eyebrows. You appear to
		others with low set
		eyebrows as being more formal and less
		approachable. In order to
		appear more friendly wear softer colors, be
		more expressive and speak
		with warmth in your voice. Learn to smile
		more when meeting people for
		the first time. You are just as friendly
		as anyone else once you get
		to know the other person, so show it.

	</string>
	<string name="app_trait3_type_a">
		Type A’s have closer set eyes. By nature you are
		intolerant of errors. You
		have a keen sense of priority and take
		immediate action to correct
		things that aren’t quite right. Punctuality
		is important to you. You
		are precise and attention to detail is
		important. When you focus on a
		task or you are under stress, others
		will see you as just tolerant or
		feel you lack tolerance.\n\n

		You are
		quickly irritated by interruptions, sloppy work and things that
		are not
		completed on time. Because you are so focused on what you are
		doing,
		you can easily get lost in your thoughts and activities. Make
		sure you
		come up for air now and again, and check in to see what’s
		happening
		around you. Your strength is that you pay attention to
		detail and stay
		focused on the task at hand. This is also a trait that
		can cause
		relationship conflicts.

	</string>
	<string name="app_trait3_type_b">
		Type B’s have evenly spaced eyes. You are the
		mediator. The person who is
		balanced between the type A and type C. You
		are more tolerant than
		Type A’s and more focused than Type C’s. To Type
		A’s you appear to be
		more like a Type C and to Type C’s you appear to
		be more like a Type A


	</string>
	<string name="app_trait3_type_c">
		Type C have wider set eyes. By nature you are
		tolerant of errors. You come across as being very laid back and very
		easy to get along with. You have a tendency to put things off until
		tomorrow and you can be easily distracted and take on too many things
		at once.\n\n

		The challenge for you is to stay focused on what you are
		doing. Try not
		to take on more than you can handle. You may tolerate
		too much, and
		when this happens you need to create more boundaries or
		otherwise
		people can take advantage of your good nature. If you have a
		tendency
		to be late, start out earlier than usual in order to get to
		appointments and meetings on time, as others can take your lateness as
		tardiness or disinterest. This is also a trait that can cause
		relationship conflicts, especially when the other person has low
		tolerance.
		
	</string>
	<string name="app_trait4_type_a">
		Type A’s can take other peoples comments and
		criticism personally. If
		someone makes a critical remark, ask what was
		meant by it and explore
		the comment further to avoid
		misunderstanding.\n\n

		Remember some people with the longer gap can come
		across as sarcastic although
		their intention was just to be amusing;
		which can get taken the wrong
		way.
	
	</string>
	<string name="app_trait4_type_b">
		Type B’s fit mid way between the two extremes.
		You’ll find some people have a dry sense of humor, possibly slightly
		sarcastic, while others seem to take your words more personally.
		Generally though, you’ll get on well with both groups, very often
		being the mediator between type A’s and type C’s. Be prepared to watch
		what you say to those with the smaller philtrum and don’t take the
		words of those with the longer philtrum personally.
	</string>
	<string name="app_trait4_type_c">
		Type C’s have a dry sense of humor, which those in
		tune with you will enjoy. However not everyone, especially those with
		a small philtrum, will understand the subtlety of your humor.\n\n

		To
		some you can also come across as being very sarcastic and cutting,
		which may not be your intent. Those with the short philtrum can take a
		harmless comment and feel very hurt, so be careful that it does not
		have a cutting edge. Remember that others may miss the subtlety of
		your humor.
		
	</string>

	<string name="app_trait5_type_a">
		Type A’s are more reflective by nature. Those with
		a thin upper lip are by nature concise when speaking. They prefer to
		talk facts with short explanations, prefer to be concise . Those with
		the smaller lower lip are by nature more reflective and think more
		before giving of their time, their possessions and of themselves.\n\n

		They appreciate interests that are expressed non verbally and when
		giving
		do so with a lot of significance and meaning.
		


	</string>
	<string name="app_trait5_type_b">
		Type B are between the two extremes. The person who
		is balanced between the type A and type C. They are more verbal and
		quick to give than Type A and more reflective before responding than
		Type C. To Type A’s they appear to be more like Type C’s and to Type
		C’s they appear to be more like Type A’s.

	</string>
	<string name="app_trait5_type_c">
		Type C’s are those with a full upper lip and are by
		nature more talkative.
		Those with the full lower lip are by nature more
		generous in the
		moment. They are open and immediate with their words
		and their deeds;
		often giving without thinking and speaking at
		length.\n\n

		They will appear to be more emotional than the other types.
		They need to
		talk and need to express themselves and with this they are
		quick to
		give; often giving too liberally, something that they may
		regret
		later.

	
	</string>
	<string name="app_trait6_type_a">
		Type A’s are less inclined to analyze situations
		and information. It doesn’t indicate that you don’t analyze, but more
		the trait indicates you like people to get to the bottom line. You are
		by nature decisive and you focus outwardly on what needs to be done.
		You just want the big picture and you’re action driven.\n\n

		You have an
		immediate understanding of what is being said and like to act
		on it
		right away. This trait also indicates that you don’t need all of
		the
		information up front to make a decision. If necessary you will go
		back
		later to check for any additional details.\n\n

		Try not to cut people
		off in the midst of their conversation or finish
		their sentences for
		them, or they will feel that you are not
		interested in what they are
		saying.
		

	</string>
	<string name="app_trait6_type_b">
		Type B’s have eyelids which are half covered by, or
		very close to the
		epicanthic fold. These are the balancers; the
		mediators. They are
		viewed by Type A’s as being Type C’s, while Type
		C’s see them more
		like Type A’s.\n\n

		You are likely to gather more
		information before making decisions than
		the type A’s, yet you will be
		viewed by the type C’s to still make
		your decisions too quickly. Learn
		to speed up when dealing with Type
		A’s and don’t cut Type C’s off when
		they are talking.

	

	</string>
	<string name="app_trait6_type_c">
		Type C’s are by nature very analytical. They focus
		inwardly on what they
		feel about a situation. They need to understand
		how and why things
		work, which makes them reluctant to make decisions
		until their
		questions have been completely satisfied.\n\n

		Try not to
		over analyze everything, otherwise you’ll find the project you
		are
		working on is being held up by your need to assess every step
		along the
		way. Decide what is most important for now, then check the
		other
		details later rather than hold up progress. When talking with
		individuals who want the bottom line, keep your responses to the
		point.

	</string>



	<string name="app_trait7_type_a">
		As a Type B you have a lack of sparkle in your
		eyes. Don’t worry though
		as you can change this by being more outgoing
		and focusing more on
		having fun. The less stress you have in your life
		contributes to
		adding sparkle to your eyes. If your wondering why other
		people seem
		to attract more people to them and they appear to be more
		popular, the
		magnetic quality of their eyes is one major reason.

	</string>
	<string name="app_trait7_type_b">
		As a Type C you have a depth of the color in your
		eyes. They have a
		magnetic quality and a sparkle that attracts people
		to you. People
		with magnetism are more alert and often more fun.\n\n

		Other people get a feeling of trust when they look into your eyes.
		Strangers will come up to you and without any reservations they will
		tell you their deepest secrets.\n\n

		They may even be overly attracted
		to you, thinking you are flirting with
		them. If you do not want this to
		happen - use body language to
		indicate it is not appropriate and
		endeavor to change the subject. The
		trait will be even stronger if you
		have the affable trait as well, and
		less so if you have the more
		discerning trait.
	
	</string>







</resources>
